Jim Jeong

13867 Laguna St., La Mirada, CA 90638 | 562-682-8331 | jsj018@ucsd.edu

Objective

 To provide consistent satisfaction and professionalism in overall work without repeating the same errors. I strive to provide a positive experience gained from prior experience, but at the same time adapt to new rules and surroundings.

Education

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA | JUNE 2009 | ABC SECONDARY SCHOOL

• 16534 Carmenita Rd., Cerritos, CA 90703

BACHELOR OF ARTS | EXPECTED JUNE 2020 | UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, SAN DIEGO

- Major: Speculative Design
- Related coursework: Design Communication, Introduction to Computing

Skills & Abilities

- Customer Service
- Microsoft Office, Excel, Outlook, PowerPoint
- Adobe Photoshop, Acrobat, Illustrator

Experience

QUALITY CONTROL COORDINATOR | BIZZ, INC. | JANUARY 2016-2017

• Oversaw the shipping/receiving of imported goods for the distribution of women's apparel to major department stores, while complying with quality control standards set forth by vendors.

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE | FASHION BELLA, LLC | JUNE 2013 - JANUARY 2016

Answered phone calls and replied to e-mails from customers throughout the United States regarding
questions or concerns about the company's e-commerce website.

GOLD STAR | ELEMENTARY SCHOOL TUTOR | SEPTEMBER 2012 - JUNE 2013

• Ensured the completion of homework and extracurricular assignments for designated students attending the after-school program.

Extracurricular/Volunteer

CMC MEXICO MISSIONS 2018 | CERRITOS MISSION CHURCH | AUGUST 2018

• Participated in a 3-day mission trip to my church's mission center in Primo Tapia, Mexico to evangelize to the surrounding community about the Gospel and provided school supplies for children.